Guide to the Eddy LaDue papers, 1963-2004.
LaDue, Eddy papers
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Eddy LaDue papers, 1963-2004.
21-43-4270
LaDue, Eddy L.
4 cubic feet.
Publications, photographs, and course material.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Includes LaDue's publications, course material for Agricultural Finance, photographs of the Bankers School of Agriculture (1963-1977), and records of the Northeast School of Agricultural Lending (2003-2004) and the W.I. Myers Agricultural Finance and Management Advisory Council (1997-2004).
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
Professor of Applied Economics and Management at Cornell University.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Includes LaDue's publications, course material for Agricultural Finance, photographs of the Bankers School of Agriculture (1963-1977), and records of the Northeast School of Agricultural Lending (2003-2004) and the W.I. Myers Agricultural Finance and Management Advisory Council (1997-2004).
SUBJECTS
Names:
LaDue, Eddy L.; LaDue, Eddy L.; Bankers School of Agriculture.; Cornell University -- Faculty.; New York State College of Agriculture and Life Sciences. Dept. of Applied Economics and Management.; Northeast School of Agricultural Lending.
Subjects:
Agriculture -- Accounting -- Standards -- New York (State); Dairy farms -- Finance.; Farm management.; Agriculture -- Finance.; Agriculture -- Economic aspects.
Form and Genre Terms:
Photographs.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- Farm Finance course 405, 1976-2004 (Box 1)
- Farm Finance course 405, 1989-2004 (Box 2)
- Agricultural Finance course 405, 2003-2004 (Box 3)
- Northeast School of Agricultural Lending, 2003-2004 (Box 3)
- Northeast School of Agricultural Lending, 2004- (Box 4)
- W.I. Myers Agricultural Finance and Management Advisory Council, 1997-2004 (Box 4)
- Agricultural economics history, 1932-1987 (Box 4)
- LaDue publications, 1997-2001 (Box 4)
- Photographs of Bankers School of Agriculture, 1963-1977 (Box 4)
- Correspondence with Bill Myers, 1963-1976 (Box 4)
- Transcript of interview with Bill Myers, 1964 (Box 4)